OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23) 6178/023
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
2003- 2015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States. Department of Labor
United States. Office of Labor-Management Standards (OLMS)
6178/023
7 cubic feet
7 linear ft.
Collect bargaining agreements.
9134839
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 12, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 14, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm
9134839
- Code no.12: UFCW Local 27 and Pathmark Stores, Inc., 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Code no.14, Midwest Generation, LLC and IBEW Local 15, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Code no.22: UAW and UAW Local Union 848 and Vought Aircraft, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Code no.206: Keebler Company and Baker, Confectionary, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers International Union Local 253, 2006- 2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Code no.210: KRAFT Foods Global and United Food and Commercial Workers International Union, 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Code no.253: California Processors, Inc. and Teamsters California State Council of Cannery and Food Processing Unions, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Code no.259: Weyerhaeuser Paper Co. and Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Code no.298: Michigan Sugar Co. and Bakery, Confectionary, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers Locals 259-G through 262-G, 2005- 2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Code no.445: Swift & Co., Louisville KT and United Food and Commercial Workers Local 227, 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Code no.876: Greater Blouse, Skirt, and Undergarment Association, Metro Area Apparel Manufacturing Association, Sportswear Apparel Association and Blouse, Skirt, Sportswear, Children's Wear and Allied Workers' Union Local 23-25, Amalgamated Ladies' Garmen, 2007-2010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Code no.1010: SNE Enterprises and Midwestern Council of Industrial Workers of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 2004-2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Code no.1031: Roseburg Forest Products Co. and Carpenters Industrial Council Local 2949, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Code no.1033: International Paper Co. and United Steel, Paper and Forestry, Rubber, Manufacturing, Energy, Allied Industrial and Service Workers International Union, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Code no.1131: Manufacturing Woodworkers Association of Greater New York Inc. and District Council of New York City and Vicinity of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 2007-2012 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Code no.1419: Metropolitan Lithographers Association Inc. and Amalgamated Lithographers of America Local 1, 2005-2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Code no.1683: PPG Industries Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Local 470, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Code no.2308: Corning Inc. and United Steel, Paper and Forestry, Rubber, Manufacturing, Energy, Allied Industrial and Service Workers International Union Local 1000, 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Code no.2350 Automated Machine Department Workers, St. Gobain Containers and Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics & Allied Workers International Union Locals 30, 39, 50, 71, 75, 111, 121, 125, 166, 169, 193, 222, 226, 239, 253, 254, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Code no.2357: Production and Maintenance Workers, St. Gobain Containers and Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics & Allied Workers International Union Locals 30, 39, 54, 87, 96, 111, 117, 125, 166, 169, 193, 222, 226, 253, 254, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Code no.2531: US Steel Tubular Products Inc. and United Steel, Paper and Forestry, Rubber, Manufacturing, Energy, Allied Industrial Services Workers International Union, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Code no.3222: Deere & Co. and UAW Locals 281, 450, 94, 865, 74, 79, 434, 838, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Code no.3227: Whirlpool Corporation and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers Local S-272, 2007-2010 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Code no.3278: The Timken Co. and United Steelworkers of America, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Code no.3375: Indianapolis Plant of Carrier Corp. and United Steelworkers Local 1999, 2008-2011 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Code no.3636: Herrin Laundry Products and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers District 111 Lodge 554, 2005- 2009 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Code no.3645: Fixture Division and IBEW Local 3, 2007-2010 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Code no.3786: Hoover Co. and IBEW Local 1985, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Code no.3787: Lucent Technology and Communication Workers of America (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Code no.4023 Spring Hill Site General Motors Corporation and UAW Local 1853, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Code no.4052: Bombardier Learjet and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers Local 639, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Code no.4055: The Boeing Company and Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Code no.4115: New River Valley Plant of Volvo Tucks and UAW and Local 2069 of UAW, 2008-2011 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Code no.4177: Boeing Company and Society of Professional Engineering Employees in Aerospace, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Code no.4183: Howmet Corp. and UAW Local 1243, 2005-2010 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Code no.4193 Aerospace Corp. and Aerospace Professional Staff Association, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Code no.4607: Metropolitan Association of Doll, Stuffed Toy and Plastics Manufacturers and Amalgamated, Industrial and Toy & Novelty Workers Local 223, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Code no.5719: Verizon Southwest Inc. and Communication Workers of America, 2005-2010 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Code no.5770: Verizon Northwest Inc. and IBEW Local 89, 2005-2010 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Code no.6000: Alabama Power Company and IBEW Locals 345, 833, 904, 391, 801, 841, 1053, 796, 2077, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Code no.6028: PSI Energy Inc. and IBEW Local 1393, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Code no.6030: Southern California Edison and IBEW Local 47, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Code no.6060: UWUA Local 175 and Dayton Power and Light Co., 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Code no.6061: Detroit Edison, MichCon, DTE Energy Corporate Services LLC and Utility Workers Union of America Local 223, 2007- 2010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Code no.6076: Public Service Electric & Gas Company and UWUA Local 601, 2005-2011 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Code no.6089: Central Hudson Gas & Electric Corporation and IBEW Local 320, 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Code no.6094: Edison and Utility Workers Union of America Local 246 and Edison and IBEW Local 47, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Code no.6106: Alabama Power Company and IBEW Locals 345, 833, 904, 391, 801, 1053, 796, 2077, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Code no.6301: Macy's Northwest and UFCW Local 21, 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Code no.6325: Ready Mix and Material Agreement Cook County Illinois and Building Material, Lumber, Box, Shaving, Roofing and Insulating Chauffeurs, Teamsters, Warehousemen and Helpers, and Related Industry Employees, Watchmen and Security Guards Union Loc, 2005-2010 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Code no.6331: Industrial Employers and Distributors Association and Warehouse Union Local 6 and 17 ILWU, 2007-2010 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Code no.6336: Kroger Co. and United Food and Commercial Workers Union, Local 536, 2004-2009 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Code no.6354: Dominick's Finer Foods, LLC and UFCW Local 1546, 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Code no.6359: Safeway Inc. and UFCW Local 1496, 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Code no.6360: T/A Shoppers Food and Pharmacy and UFCW Local 27, 2004-2009 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Code no.6376: King Kullen Grocery Co. and UFCW Local 1500, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Code no.6377: The Stop and Shop Supermarket Co. and UFCW Local 1500, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Code no.6378: D'Agostino Supermarkets Inc. and UFCW Local 1500, 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Code no.6381: Waldbaums Supermarkets and UFCW Local 342, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Code no.6500: Bloomingdale's and RWDSU Local 3, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Code no.6701: Acme Markets, Inc. and UFCW Local 1245, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Code no.6703: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Akron-Canton Food Industry Committee and UFCW Local 880, 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Code no.6709: Kings Super Market and UFCW Local 1245, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Code no.6711: Tops Markets, LLC and UFCW Local 1, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Code no.6712: Tops Buffalo and UFCW Local 1, 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Code no.6713: Tops- Rochester and United Food & Commercial Workers International Union Local 1, 2006-2008 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Code no.6719: Gristedes and UFCW Local 1500, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Code no.6726: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc., Superfresh and UFCW Local 27, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Code no.6745: Jewel Food Stores, Inc. and UFCW Local 881, 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Code no.6755: Safeway Inc. and UFCW Locals 5, 101, 648 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Code no.6758: Safeway Inc. and UFCW Local 400 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Code no.6764: Meijer Stores Ltd. Partnership Stores 148, 150, 151, 157, 159, 223, 224 and UFCW Local 1099, 2005-2010 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Code no.6779: Safeway Stores, Inc. and UFCW Local 7, 2004-2009 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Code no.6805: Giant Food LLC and UFCW Local 27, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Code no.6855: Riverside Division of Penn Traffic and UFCW Local 23, 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Code no.6860: Dominick's Finer Foods, LLC and UFCW Local 1546, 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Code no.6864: Raley's, Albertson's Inc., Smith's Food & Drug Stores & Von's and Local 711, 2001- 2004 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Code no.6870: Bruno's Supermarkets Inc. and UFCW Local 1657, 2005-2009 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Code no.6872: King Soopers Inc. and UFCW Local 7, 2004-2009 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Code no.6875: Safeway Inc. and UFCW Local 27, 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Code no.6876: Giant and UFCW Local 400 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Code no.6883: King Soopers and UFCW Local 7, 2004-2009 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Code no.6886: Safeway Stores, Inc. and UFCW Local 7, 2004-2009 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Code no.6895: Pathmark Stores, Inc. and UFCW Local 1500, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Code no.6896: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and UFCW Local 342, 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Code no.6917: St. Paul Automobile Dealers Association and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers District Lodge 77, 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Code no.7310: CVS and UFCW Local 1099, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Code no.7419: Horizon Blue Cross Blue Shield of New Jersey and Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 32, 2005- 2010 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Code no.7425: Blue Cross Blue Shield of Michigan and UAW and Locals 1781, 2145, 2256, 2500, 2005-2008 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Code no.7426: San Francisco Maintenance Contractors Association and Service Employees International Union Local 87 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Code no.7532: Delaware North Companies Parks and Resorts at Yosemite and Service Employees International Union Local 535, 2005- 2008 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Code no.77112: Western States Regional Join Board Local 52 and Textile Rental Association Associates, 2006-2009 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Code no.7904: News Media Guild, The Newspaper Guild- Communications Workers of America, Local 31222 and Associated Press, 2005- 2008 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Code no.7912: Alliance of Motion Picture and Television Producers and Screen Actors Guild, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Code no. 7913: Alliance of Motion Picture and Television Producers and Screen Actors Guild, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Code no.7919: Sound Recording Special Payments Fund Agreement, Sound Recording Trust Agreement and American Federation of Musicians, 2002-2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Code no.7943: NSTAR Electric & Gas Corporation and Utility Workers Union of America and UWUA Local 369, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Code no.7950: Alliance of Motion Picture and Television Producers and Writers Guild of America, 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Code no.7960: United Association Plumbers Local Union 15 and Minnesota Mechanical Contractors Association, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Code no.7965, 7966: Pipefitters Local 539 and Minnesota Mechanical Contractors Association, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Code no.7967: Pipefitters Local 455, Plumbers Local 34 and Minnesota Mechanical Contractors Association, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Code no.7969: Directors Guild of America Basic Agreement and Directors Guild of America Freelance Live and Tape Television Agreement, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Code no.7980: SEIU Local 113 and Fairview Southdale, Park Nicollet Methodist, University of Minnesota, Children's, HealthEast Bethesda and HealthEast St. John's Hospitals, 2006-2009 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Code no.8005: Montefiore Medical Center and New York State Nurses Association, 2005-2009 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Code no.8006: Dimensions Healthcare System and SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Local 1199, 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Code no.8017: New York Presbyterian Hospital, Columbia Presbyterian Center and New York State Nurses Association, 2005-2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Code no.8037: Abbott Northwestern Hospital, Mercy Hospital, Phillips Eye Institute, United Hospital and SEIU Local 113, 2006- 2008 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Code no.8068: International Union of Operating Engineers and Nevada Contractors Association, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Code no.8072: Tri-State Contractors Association and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 181, 2005-2010 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Code no.8075: Associated General Contractors of Indiana and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 181, 2006-2009 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Code no.8076: The Smithfield Packing Co. Inc. and Food Processors Local 1046, 2006-2009 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Code no.8083: Nevada Contractors Association and Southwest Regional Council of Carpenters and Affiliated Locals, 2007-2011 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Code no.8095: The International Union of Operating Engineers Local 139 and Allied Construction Employers Association, Associated General Contractors, 2006-2011 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Code no.8106: Avaya and Communications Workers of America, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Code no.8107: Avaya and IBEW Locals 21, 134, 206, 827, 2222, 2320-2327, 2006-2009 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Code no.8113: IBEW Local 357 and Southern Nevada Chapter NECA, 2006-2009 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Code no.8115: United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry and Northern California Contractors Association and Industrial Contractors, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Code no.8153: Laborers International Union of North America Local 17 and Construction Contractors Association of the Hudson Valley, 2007- 2009 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Code no.8160: Empire State Regional Council of Carpenters and Independent Contractors, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Code no.8169: The Associated General Contractors of Missouri and the Western Missouri and Kansas Laborers' District Council and Affiliated Locals, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Code no.8170: Associated General Contactors of Missouri and Operating Engineers Local 101, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Code no.8172: Associated General Contractors of Missouri and Teamsters Joint Council No.13, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Code no.8173: Associated General Contractors of Missouri and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners and Affiliated Locals, 2006- 2010 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Code no.8176: Associated General Contractors of Missouri and Teamsters Joint Council no.56, 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Code no.8179: Iron Workers District Council of he State of Texas and Texas Iron Workers Employers' Association, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Code no.8181: Contractors Association of Eastern Pennsylvania and Teamster Local Union 312 Tuck Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Local 384, General Teamsters, Chauffeurs Helpers and Yardmen, Local 470, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Code no.8186: Eastern Contractors Association and Bricklayers and Allied Craftworkers Local 2, 2008-2013 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Code no.8193: District Council of Northern New Jersey, International Association of Bridge, Structural, Ornamental and Reinforcing Iron Workers and New Jersey Steel Association and Rigging Contractors of New Jersey, 2008-2011 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Code no.8198: New England Regional Council of Carpenters Local 94 and Construction Industries of Rhode Island, 2005-2009 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Code no.8204: Nevada Contractors Association, Associated General Contactors and Teamsters Union Local 631, 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Code no.8213: IBEW Local 728 and South Florida Chapter, NECA, Inc., 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Code no.8221: International Union of Painters and Allied Trades and Northern Ohio Painting and Taping Contractors Association, 2005- 2009 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Code no.8320: BHP Copper Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America Local 104, International Union of Operating Engineers Local 428, IBEW Local 518, The United Steel, Paper and Forestry, Rubber, Manufa, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Code no.8327: Allied Division of Delaware Contractors Association and Metropolitan Regional Council of Philadelphia and Vicinity, and Carpenters Local 626 of United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Code no.8332: IBEW and Mass Electric Construction Company, 2009-2015 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Code no.8345: Stanford Hospital and Clinics & Lucile Packard Children's Hospital & Service Employees International Union, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Code no.8427: The Painting and Decorating Contractors of America and Southwest Regional Council of Carpenters and Affiliated Local Unions, International Union of Painters, 2007-2011 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Code no.8428: Associated General Contractors of Washington and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Locals 38, 174, 231, 252, 313, 589, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Code no.8431: Construction Industry Council of Westchester and Hudson Valley and International Union of Operating Engineers Locals 137, 137A, 137B, 137C, 137R, 2008-2011 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Code no.8457: AGC/CCIA Building Contractors Labor Division of Connecticut and Mason Contractors Association of Connecticut Local 1 of International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen, 2006-2012 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Code no.8477: International Union of Operating Engineers Local 542 and Contractors Association of Eastern Pennsylvania, 2006- 2010 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Code no.8486: Connecticut Construction Industries Association and Connecticut Laborers' District Council of the Laborers International Union of North America, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Code no.8495: Heavy Construction Laborers' Locals no.1290 and 663 of Western Missouri and Kansas and Heavy Constructors' Association of the Greater Kansas City Area, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Code no.8510: National Fire Sprinkler Association and Road Sprinkler Fitters Union Local 669, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Code no.8512: Plumbing Contractors Association of Chicago and Cook County and Chicago Journeymen Plumbers' Local 130, 2007- 2010 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Code no.: The Builders' Association and Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades District Council 3, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Code no.8532: IBEW Local 11 and Los Angeles County Chapter National Electrical Contractors Association, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Code no.8538: IBEW Local 6 and San Francisco Electrical Contractors Association, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Code no.8557: International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen Local 1 NY and Building Restoration Contractors Association, 2008- 2012 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Code no.8571: Millwrights Local Union 1102 and Michigan Conveyor Manufacturers Association and Associated General Contractors Greater Detroit Chapter, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Code no.8575: Sheet Metal Workers' International Association Local 28 and Sheet Metal & Air Conditioning Association and SMACNA of Long Island, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Code no.8576: Sheet Metal Workers' International Association Local 105 and Air Conditioning Sheet Metal Association, 2006- 2009 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Code no.8593: Connecticut Construction Industries Association and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 478, 2008- 2011 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Code no.8599: Illinois Environmental Contractors Association and Construction and General Laborers' District Council of Chicago and Vicinity and Laborers Local 225, 2006-2010 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Code no.8604: Laborers' District of Ohio Laborers' International Union of North America and Ohio Contractors Association Labor Relations Division, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Code no.8605: International Union of Operating Engineers Local 18 and The labor Relations Division of the Ohio Contactors Association, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Code no.8606: Operating Engineers 302, 612 Agreement with Associated General Contractors of Washington, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Code no.8627: General Contractors Association of New York and District Council of Carpenters of New York City and Vicinity for Dockbuilders Local 1456, 2006-2011 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Code no.8630: Central Illinois Builders of AGC, Builders Association of Tazewell County Greater Peoria Contactors & Suppliers Association and Mid-Central Illinois Regional Council of Carpenters, 2006-2009 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Code no.8634: Steel and Iron Contractors Association, Construction Employers Association of Cleveland and International Association of Bridge, Structural, Ornamental and Reinforcing Iron Workers Local 17, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 25)